Guide to the Anne Draper Papers, 1938-1973
Department of Special Collections
- SERIES IV: AGRICULTURAL LABOR -- SUBJECT FILES, 1951-1972
  - Krebs, Al V., Jr., Agribusiness Accountability Project, 1971 13 9 Krebs, Al V., Jr., Agribusiness Accountability Project, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Mechanization, 1960-1971 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Migrant labor, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Migrant labor, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Migrant labor, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Migrant labor, 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Migrant labor, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Migrant labor, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Migrant labor, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Minimum wage, 1960-1969 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, 1957-1959 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, Jan.-June 1960 14 3 Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, July-Dec. 1960 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, Jan.-June 1961 14 5 Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, July-Dec. 1961 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, Jan.-June 1964 14 9 Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, July-Dec. 1964 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, Jan. 1965 14 11 Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, Feb. 1965 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, Mar. 1965 15 1 Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, Apr. 1965 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, May 1965 15 3 Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, June 1965 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, July 1965 15 5 Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, Aug. 1965 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, Sept. 1965 15 7 Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, Oct. 1965 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, Nov. 1965 15 9 Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, Dec. 1965 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, Jan.-Feb. 1966 15 11 Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, Mar. 1966 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, Apr. 1966 16 1 Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, May-June 1966 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, July-Aug. 1966 16 3 Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, Sept.-Oct. 1966 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, Nov.-Dec. 1966 16 5 Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, Jan. 1967 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, Feb.-Mar. 1967 16 7 Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, Apr.-June 1967 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, July-Aug. 1967 17 2 Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, Sept.-Oct. 1967 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, Nov.-Dec. 1967 17 4 Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, Jan.-Mar. 1968 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, Apr.-June 1968 17 6 Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, July 1968 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, Aug. 1968 17 8 Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, Sept. 1968 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, Oct. 1968 18 1 Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, Nov.-Dec. 1968 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, Jan.-Feb. 1969 18 3 Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, Mar.-Apr. 1969 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, May 1969 18 5 Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, June 1969 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, July 1969 18 7 Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, Aug. 1969 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, Sept.-Oct. 1969 19 2 Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, Nov.-Dec. 1969 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, Jan.-Mar. 1970 19 4 Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, Apr. 1970 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, May 1970 19 6 Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, June 1970 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, July 1970 19 8 Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, Aug. 1970 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, Sept.-Oct. 1970 19 10 Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, Nov.-Dec. 1970 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, Jan.-Mar. 1971 20 2 Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, Apr.-June 1971 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, July-Sept. 1971 20 4 Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, Oct.-Dec. 1971 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, Jan.-Mar. 1972 20 6 Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, Apr.-July 1972 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, Aug.-Oct. 1972 20 8 Newsclippings on agriculture and farm labor, Nov.-Dec. 1972 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Pesticides, 1963-1971 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Pesticides, newsclippings, 1963-1971 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Proposition 22 (Agricultural Labor Relations Initiative), 1972 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Public Law 78/Braceros, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Public Law 78/Braceros, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Public Law 78/Braceros, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Public Law 78/Braceros, 1962-1963 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Public Law 78/Braceros, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Public Law 78/Braceros, 1965-1967 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Public Law 78/Braceros, newsclippings, 1959-1965 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Public Law 414/Braceros, hearings, correspondence May 1964 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Public Law 414/Braceros, hearings, testimony May 1964 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Public Law 414/Braceros, hearings, Dec. 2, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Public Law 414/Braceros, hearings, miscellany Dec. 7, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Public Law 414/Braceros, hearings, newsclippings Dec. 7, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Public Law 414/Braceros, hearings, testimony Dec. 7, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Public Law 414/Braceros, hearings, Jan. 1965 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Public Law 414/Braceros, hearings, Jan. 1968 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Puerto Rican farm workers, 1964-1970 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Resolutions concerning farm labor, 1959-1965 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Sugar beets, 1954-1966 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Sugar beets, 1967-1972 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Sugar beets, newsclippings, 1959-1972 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Unemployment insurance for farm laborers, 1962-1970 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - University of California, farm labor reports, 1963-1964 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Water/160-acre limitation, 1964-1971 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Wirtz, Willard W., newsclippings, 1964-1965 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Wirtz, Willard W., statements and reports, 1964-1966 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1959-1971 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- SERIES V: PHOTOGRAPHS, ca. 1961-1966
  - Children working in the fields (prints), ca. 1965 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Delano Grape Strike (prints), ca. 1966 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Draper, Anne, (prints) ca. 1963-1964 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Imperial Valley Lettuce Strike (negatives), ca. 1961 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - El Malcriado newspaper staff (prints), n.d. (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - San Francisco Labor Council Food Caravan (prints), Dec. 1965 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- OVERSIZED ITEMS
  - Citizens for Farm Labor recruitment display boards (2), n.d. (1-2)
  - "The Draper Caper - A Search for America," n.d. (3)
  - National Farm Workers Association, "Caravana para los huelgistas de Delano," n.d. (4)
  - National Farm Workers Association, "Council for Justice Presents El Teatro Campesino de Delano", n.d. (5)
  - National Farm Workers Association, "Peregrinacion, penitencia, revolucion," n.d. (6)
  - United Farm Workers Organizing Committee, Delano Boycott March, July 9, 1966 (7)
  - United Farm Workers Organizing Committee, "Huelga-Don't Buy Perelli-Minetti Products," n.d. (8)
  - United Farm Workers Organizing Committee, calendar 1971 (9)
  - United Farm Workers Organizing Committee, "Say `No!' to Grapes, Symbols of Human Misery" (10)